okay um I learned this from Jim Smitty
diesel um I've actually thought about
this for a long time but I never
actually got around to trying it but one
problem with the glute hamr is that when
you come up to the top there's no
tension on the hamstrings it's unloaded
so you kind of um you elevate the back
here I put it up onto a box squat but
what this does is it you know it changes
the angle to now when you're up towards
the top of the movement it's still under
tension so you get constant tension on
the hamstring so anyway I toyed around
with it and I love it it's a better way
in my opinion it's a better way to do
glute ham raises and um you know the
manufacturers should start playing
around with this um design because you
really get a better hamstring workout in
my opinion um but I mean here's what it
looks like
see up top I'm under like I'm my
hamstrings are about to cramp right
now
so um last night I did a a a workout I
got three sets of six I can normally get
like three sets of 10 to 12 when this is
not elevated when it's straight so give
it a try it's in my opinion a better way
to do glute ham raises and uh thanks
thanks Smitty great idea